[
  {
    "front": "je, moi",
    "back": "私"
  },
  {
    "front": "nom",
    "back": "名"
  },
  {
    "front": "avant, auparavant, devant",
    "back": "前"
  },
  {
    "front": "derrière, après, plus tard",
    "back": "後"
  },
  {
    "front": "midi",
    "back": "午"
  },
  {
    "front": "chaque, tous les -",
    "back": "毎"
  },
  {
    "front": "heure, temps, moment",
    "back": "時"
  },
  {
    "front": "durée, espace, intervalle",
    "back": "間"
  },
  {
    "front": "minute, part, comprendre, séparer, diviser",
    "back": "分"
  },
  {
    "front": "moitié, milieu, demi",
    "back": "半"
  }
]
